Guide to the Wade Hall 8 track tapes PM.012
University Libraries Division of Special Collections, The University of Alabama
- Box 37
  - Do It All Night - Curtis Mayfield - Curtom Records, 1978. (M8U 5-22) (Box 37)
  - Make Love To The Music - Leon and Mary Russell - Paradise Records, 1977 (Box 37)
  - Love Is In The Air - John Paul Young - Scott Brothers Records, 1978. (TP 7101) (Box 37)
  - Cupid's Arrow - David Blue - Elektra/Asylum, 1976. (ET-81077) (Box 37)
  - Nightingale - Gilberto Gil - Elektra/Asylum, 1979. (ET-8167) (Box 37)
  - The Sanford/Townsend Band - Warner Bros., 1976., 2.0 (Box 37)
- Box 38
  - Spanish 1 - Institute for Language Study - Ampex, 1967. (LSC 8501) (Box 38)
  - 43 Great Opera Masterpieces Vol. 1 - Decca, 1972. (68 20 0450) (Box 38)
  - Andrew Watts/Leonard Bernstein Tchaikovsky Piano Concerto No. 1 - New York Philharmonic - Columbia, 1974. (MA 33071) (Box 38)
  - The Best Loved Music of Tchaikovsky: A Festival of Glory Music Tape 1 - The Reader's Digest Association - RCA Records, 1975. (RD 8-5366 RD 5-178-1/1) (Box 38)
  - I Like Tchaikovsky - Carmen Dragon - Capitol, no date. (8XP 8617) (Box 38)
  - Pride of Country Music - Charley Pride - RCA Records, 1967. (P8S-1278) (Box 38)
  - Soul of Country Music - Connie Smith - RCA Records, no date. (P8S 1288), n.d. (Box 38)
  - This Is My Valley - The Singing Rambos - no information. (#1038), n.d. (Box 38)
  - Two Sides Of The Moon - Keith Moon - MCA Records, 1975. (MCAT - 2136) (Box 38)
  - The Souther, Hillman, Furay Band - Elektra/Asylum, 1974. (ET-81006) (Box 38)
  - "Gentle On My Mind" And Other Originals - John Hartford - RCA, no date. (P8S 1425) (Box 38)
  - Cooper Brothers - Capricorn Records, 1978. (M8N-0206) (Box 38)
  - Jukebox Saturday Night: 96 Great Jukebox Hits Tape 2 1940-1944 - Reader's Digest Association - RCA Records, 1975. (RD 5-139-1/2 RD 8-5333) (Box 38)
  - The Old Way - Marty Robbins - no information. (C-437), n.d. (Box 38)
  - A Special Part Of Me - Johnny Mathis - Columbia, 1984. (FAC 38718) (Box 38)
  - Mirror - Graham Central Station - Warner Bros., 1976. (M8 2937) (Box 38)
  - Bridge Over Troubled Waters - Simon and Garfunkel - Columbia, no date. (18 10 0750) (Box 38)
- Box 39
  - Nightingale - Gilberto Gil - Elektra/Asylum, 1979. (ET-8167), 3.0 (Box 39)
  - Hardcore Jollies - Funkadelic - Warner Bros., 1976. (M8 2973), 3.0 (Box 39)
  - One Nation Under Groove - Funkadelic - Warner Bros., 1978. (M8 3209), 2.0 (Box 39)
  - Fantasy - Aquarian Dream - Elektra/Asylum, 1978. (ET- 8152) (Box 39)
  - Do It All Night - Curtis Mayfield - Curtom Records, 1978. (M8U 5022), 2.0 (Box 39)
  - Fly With Me - Supermax - Elektra/Asylum, 1979. (ET-8193) (Box 39)
  - Duo Glide - Sanford and Townsend - Warner Bros., 1977. (Box 39)
  - From The Inside - Alice Cooper - Warner Bros., 1978. (M8 3263) (Box 39)
  - So Soon We Change - David Ruffin - Warner Bros., 1979. (M8 3306) (Box 39)
  - Extension Of A Man - Donny Hathaway - Atco Records, 1973. (ATC QT-7029 0798) (Box 39)
- Box 40
  - Feels So Right - Alabama - RCA, 1981. (AHS1-3930) (Box 40)
  - I Reserve The Right - Stillwater - Capricorn Records, 1978. (M8N-0210) (Box 40)
  - So So Satisfied - Ashford & Simpson - Warner Bros., 1977. (Box 40)
  - All This And Heaven Too - Andrew Gold - Elektra/Asylum, 1978. (ET-8116) (Box 40)
  - The Whole World's Dancing - The Trammps - Atlantic, 1979. (TP 19210) (Box 40)
  - On Broadway - Robert Goulet - Columbia, no date. (18 10 0038), n.d. (Box 40)
  - We're Gonna Hold On - George & Tammy - Epic, 1973. (EA 32757) (Box 40)
  - Golden Hits - Roger Williams - Kapp Records, no date. (L-52-3530), n.d. (Box 40)
  - Dean Martin's Greatest Hits! Vol. 1 - Dean Martin - Reprise Records, no date. (M86301), n.d. (Box 40)
  - Frank Sinatra's Greatest Hits! - Frank Sinatra - Reprise Records, no date. (8FH-1025), n.d. (Box 40)
  - The Fabulous 50s vol. 2 - Columbia House/Columbia Musical Treasures, no date. (68 20 0278), n.d. (Box 40)
  - Moody Blue - Elvis Presley - RCA, 1977. (AFS1-2428) (Box 40)
  - The Best of Charley Pride vol. 3 - Charley Pride - RCA, 1976. (APS1-2023) (Box 40)
  - Sweet Country - Charley Pride - RCA, 1973. (APS1-0217). (Box 40)
  - From Monty, With Love - Mantovani and His Orchestra - London, no date. (LEL 72180). (Box 40)
  - Mantovani in Concert (From the Royal Festival Hall, London) - Mantovani and His Orchestra - London, no date. (LEM 72174) (Box 40)
  - Breakfast at Tiffany's - Henry Mancini and His Orchestra - RCA Victor, no date. (P8S 1064) (Box 40)
  - The Best of Mario Lanza vol. 1 - Mario Lanza - RCA, no date. (R8S 1130)., n.d. (Box 40)
- Box 41
  - Dueling Banjos - Challenge Corp. 1973 (Box 41)
  - Danny Davis and Willie Nelson with the Nashville Brass - RCA, 1980 (Box 41)
  - Best of Elvis Presley vol. II, n.d. (Box 41)
  - We Should be Together - Crystal Gayle - Liberty/United Records, 1979. (Box 41)